<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Viralogy</title>
    <link>http://viralogy.digital/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Viralogy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Viralogy Digital is made in Michigan.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="http://viralogy.digital/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Content</title>
      <link>http://viralogy.digital/services/content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://viralogy.digital/services/content/</guid>
      <description>Content services Article writing Includes research and drafting of SEO-oriented articles or press releases to match chosen style guides, along with photography if required.
View a sample written for the Motley Fool.
The Neighborhood Coffee Shop That Shaped Starbucks&amp;#39; Future A small, unbranded coffee shop served as a secret testing ground for the company and its new premium strategy. There is a sharp contrast between the new Starbucks (NASDAQ:SBUX) Reserve Roastery &amp;amp; Tasting Room and the neighborhood cafe a mile away, Roy Street Coffee &amp;amp; Tea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing</title>
      <link>http://viralogy.digital/services/marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://viralogy.digital/services/marketing/</guid>
      <description>Marketing Content Strategy Includes developing target profiles and subject matter, planning distribution, and analyzing performance with analytics.
Crowdfunding Includes campaign and asset creation, promotion, and hand-holding through to the final goal.
View sample coverage from Detroit Institute of Bagel&#39;s &#34;Save the Bagels&#34; campaign, which raised $10,000.
     SEO analysis Includes reviewing current keywords and generating targets in order to elevate your search presence and attract more traffic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Design</title>
      <link>http://viralogy.digital/services/web-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://viralogy.digital/services/web-design/</guid>
      <description>Web design WordPress sites Includes developing custom themes, applying premium themes, integrations, or migrations.
View a sample built for the Detroit Institute of Bagels.
     Custom builds Includes design, coding, domain set up and publishing.
View a sample created for a wedding.
     Ecommerce sites Includes integration with third-party services such as Shopify.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>